Aman Gupta

Software Developer

Gurugram, India

aman16sep2k@gmail.com

9166118650

cdaman123

in cdaman

SKILLS

Angular

Nestjs

Web Development

Java Script

TypeScript

Golang

Python

AWS

Docker

Kubernetes

INTERESTS

Deep Learning

Music

Reading

LANGUAGES

Hindi

Expert



English

Proficient



Software Developer, with endless drive to upgrade my skills. Has worked on projects based on Angular, Nestjs, Go, Machine Learning/Deep Learning/Data Science and AWS etc. have extensive knowledge of JavaScript and Python. Loves working with new technologies. Passionately interested in deep learning and neural networks.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Incubate IND

(Dec 2019 - Dec 2020)

Core Team Member- Fellows Jaipur Chapter

Organise community events for the Fellows Jaipur Chapter.

Internity Foundation

(Jan 2020 - Dec 2020)

Data Science Intern

During internship, I worked on various tools in Data Science and worked on server side log analysis project in which parse the server logs to get information about various attacks on servers. I got the best intern title for this internship.

Docquity

(Jan 2022 - Present)

Software Developer

At Docquity, I have worked on several applications that use real-time communication protocols, microservice architecture and clean coding. I worked on tools such as Angular, Nestjs, Python and Golang. I also worked on the infrastructure side such as AWS cloud, Docker, Kubernetes, including tasks using Keda. I researched the best available technologies for use in several scenarios.

EDUCATION

Udacity

(Jan 2019 - Jan 2020)

AI, Artificial Intelligence

WorldQuant University

(Jan 2019 - Jan 2020)

Data Science

Birla Institute of Technology, Mesra

(Jul 2018 - Jun 2022)

8.2

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science